What are your marketing
and distribution channels?
(Penny:)The waitresses at my work,
and this cute shop...
(Sheldon:)Hush, hush, hush. Virtually nonexistent.
(Sheldon:)I'm thinking that we set her up with a
hosted turnkey e-commerce system to start.
(Howard:)Eliminate the middle man.
(Howard:)A small server farm
with a static IP in her bedroom.
- She'll need some kind of cooling system.
- Of course.
(Sheldon:)But before we set up
a marketing infrastructure...
(Sheldon:)...we should finish optimizing
the manufacturing process.
(Sheldon:)She has a terrible problem
with moisture-induced glitter clump.
(Penny:)Yeah, it's a bitch.
Ah, I've seen this before.
- Where?
- It's a common stripper problem.
(Howard:)They dance, they sweat, they clump.
(Penny:)Ew.
(Leonard:)Thinking about adding a desiccant
like calcium sulfate?
(Howard:)Actually, I'm thinking
about this one stripper named Vega.